<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Touring Vancouver</string>
    <string name="title_activity_category_page">CategoryPage</string>
    <string name="foodsCategory">Best Food in Town</string>
    <string name="parksCategory">Beautiful Parks</string>
    <string name="beachesCategory">Beaches Everywhere</string>
    <string name="gamesCategory">Entertainment Galore</string>
    
    //Beaches
    <string name="wreck">Wreck Beach is a popular clothing-optional beach 
        located in Pacific Spirit Regional Park, which is in turn part of 
        the University Endowment Lands just west of Vancouver, British 
        Columbia, Canada.</string>
    <string name="jericho">A Vancouver beach located west of the seaside 
        neighbourhood of Kitsilano. It is surrounded by Jericho Beach Park, 
        a grassy area with a pond, which is a picnic destination.</string>
    <string name="kits">Kitsilano Beach is one of the most popular beaches 
        in Vancouver, especially in the warm summer months. Located at the 
        north edge of the Kitsilano neighbourhood, the beach faces out onto 
        Burrard Inlet.</string>
    <string name="english_bay">English Bay is located in Vancouver, British
        Columbia, Canada, west of the downtown peninsula and False Creek. It
        consists of the south side of the Burrard Inlet, extending from Point
        Grey in the southwest to Prospect Point in the northeast.</string>

    //Parks
    <string name="stanley">Stanley Park is a 405-hectare public park that 
        borders the downtown of Vancouver in British Columbia, Canada and 
        is almost entirely surrounded by waters of Vancouver Harbour and 
        English Bay.</string>
    <string name="central">Central Park is a 90-hectare urban park in
        Burnaby, British Columbia, founded in 1891. The park is on the
        Vancouver-Burnaby border, just west of the Metropolis.</string>
    <string name="grandview">Always bursting with activity, Grandview Park
        is often the site of community activities, from picnics and plays
        to festivals and concerts. In 2011, the park was upgraded with a new
        playground, pathways, stage, sport court, field house with accessible
        washrooms, lawns, gardens and restored cenotaph area.</string>
    <string name="trout_lake">Great place for dog walks, hang outs, romantic
        strolls, clearing your head, taking in the people and sounds and
        beauty of Trout Lake is a perfect way to spend some hours</string>

    //Games
    <string name="rio">The Rio Theatre is an independent, multidisciplinary
        art house in Vancouver, BC, Canada, built in 1938.</string>
    <string name="fly_over_canada">FlyOver Canada is an amazing virtual
        flight ride in which you will “take off” into a huge domed screen
        to enjoy a breathtaking flight across Canada’s most spectacular
        sights.</string>
    <string name="science">Science World at Telus World of Science,
        Vancouver is a science centre run by a not-for-profit organization
        in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada.</string>
    <string name="aquarium">The Vancouver Aquarium is a public aquarium
        located in Stanley Park in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada.</string>

    //Foods
    <string name="gotham">High-end steaks and an extensive wine list are offered
        in a snazzy art deco setting with a lounge.</string>
    <string name="firepizza">Late-night counter-serve nook serving inventive
        specialty pies and slices in an unfussy interior.</string>
    <string name="sushiyama">Sushiyama is a popular Japanese Restaurant near
        Kingsway and Broadway. They serve up affordable Japanese dishes.</string>
    <string name="warehouse">Neighborhood hangout with rustic decor and sports on
        TV serving burgers, wings and drinks.</string>
    
    //Foods Names
    <string name="gothamName">Gotham Steakhouse</string>
    <string name="firePizzaName">Fire Pizza</string>
    <string name="SushiyamaName">Sushiyama</string>
    <string name="warehouseName">The Famous Warehouse</string>
    
    //Games Names
    <string name="FlyOverName">Flyover Canada</string>
    <string name="SciWorldName">Science World</string>
    <string name="aquaName">The Vancouver Aquarium</string>
    <string name="rioName">The Rio Theatre</string>
    
    //Parks Names
    <string name="stanleyName">Stanley Park</string>
    <string name="grandName">Grandview Park</string>
    <string name="centralName">Central Park</string>
    <string name="troutName">Trout Lake Park</string>
    
    //Beaches Names
    <string name="wreckName">Wreck Beach</string>
    <string name="kitsName">Kitsilano Beach</string>
    <string name="engName">English Bay Beach</string>
    <string name="jeriName">Jericho Beach</string>
    
</resources>
